

# JOHN CRIS TAYCO

Web Developer

## ABOUT ME

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the outsourcing/offshoring industry. Skilled in Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), JavaScript, HTML. Expert in Coldfusion, Php and SQL. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Information Technology.

## CONTACT ME

Phone

+8180 7490 5132

Current Address Kashiwa City, Chiba, Japan

Home Address Davao City, Davao Del Sur, Philippines

Email bugz3jc@gmail.com

Socia

S live:bugz3jc

fb.me/stotegab

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# HTML Email Developer | APRIL, 2016 - FEBRUARY 2017

AwesomeOS (OffSourcing Philippines Inc.)

- Develop HTML for e-mail marketing campaigns based on mock up design.
- Testing in various email platforms such as Gmail, Outlook, Apple Mail etc., for debugging and compatibility using Litmus.
- Testing in actual devices in mobile and desktop, and across various operating systems.

# Frontend Developer (Shopify) | MARCH, 2017 - MAY 2017

Stealth Venture Labs ( AwesomeOS )

- Developed and maintained frontend in websites within the Shopify Platform using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Liquid.
- Worked with Project Managers for task specifications and distributions.
- Coordinated with backend developer for data specifications.
- Worked with A/B Testing tools to determine which alternate designs and layout is efficient.

## Backend Developer | JULY, 2017 - JANUARY 2020

TechStyle Fashion Group ( AwesomeOS )

- Developed and Maintained web-based tools for managing contents in an
- E-Commerce websites.
- Used HTML, CSS, JQuery for displaying data, forms and managing inputs
- Used ColdFusion with FuseBox framework as a main programming language for
- processing and communicating data to the database.
  Develop and update existing SQL Stored Procedure scripts for fetching and storing
- data in the database using SQL Server.
- Provided Technical solutions as described by task requirements.
- Addressed technical queries from users.
  Worked with QA team for testing and debugging.

### EDUCATION

JUNE 2012 - APRIL 2018

## Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

University of Mindanao

Davao City, Davao Del Sur, Philippines

#### SKILLS

Technical Personal Softwares HTML, CSS Teamwork Git SourceTree JQuery, Reactjs Innovative PHP, Codelgniter Learner Visual Studio Code ColdFusion Resourceful Python MySQL SQL Server

Spoken Language

Filipino English Japanese (basic) Others

Photography